<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Young Dynasty</title>
    <link>https://youngdynasty.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Young Dynasty</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 09:44:45 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://youngdynasty.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing Mac Apps in Go</title>
      <link>https://youngdynasty.net/posts/writing-mac-apps-in-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 09:44:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngdynasty.net/posts/writing-mac-apps-in-go/</guid>
      <description>Go makes it easy to create safe, reliable and efficient software. Concurrency is part of the language, making otherwise complicated code more intuitive to write. It can compile binaries for any non-obscure platform and has a quite capable standard library with a lively developer community.
Maybe I&amp;rsquo;m just not very clever, but even after years of using Grand Central Dispatch (&amp;ldquo;GCD&amp;rdquo;), I still find it hard to write maintainable multi-threaded code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDPR Is An Asset</title>
      <link>https://youngdynasty.net/posts/gdpr-is-an-asset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 11:28:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngdynasty.net/posts/gdpr-is-an-asset/</guid>
      <description>The General Data Protection Regulation (&amp;ldquo;GDPR&amp;rdquo;) is a regulation in European law which essentially defines how a user&amp;rsquo;s personal information must be handled. If a company serves Europeans and it does not follow these regulations, it is at risk for receiving hefty fines.
GDPR itself seems to catch a lot of negative attention within the developer community. I must say, my initial reactions were mostly negative as well. Won&amp;rsquo;t these regulations just add more friction when launching small projects?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year, Who This?</title>
      <link>https://youngdynasty.net/posts/new-year-who-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 19:22:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngdynasty.net/posts/new-year-who-this/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago, Young Dynasty officially became a registered company in France. Although there&amp;rsquo;s still quite a bit of paperwork to do in order to launch Emporter, there are plenty of things I&amp;rsquo;ve learned along the way that I&amp;rsquo;d like to share with the community.
This year, I intend to post about interesting engineering solutions, product development, and anything else related to launching, managing and using Emporter.
As a one-person company with one product to launch, it&amp;rsquo;s going to be an exciting year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://youngdynasty.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngdynasty.net/about/</guid>
      <description>Young Dynasty is a one-person company ran by me, Mikey.
I&amp;rsquo;m a full-stack software developer currently located in Paris, France. I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing code for over a decade on multiple platforms.
Aside from freelancing, I manage, develop, and design Emporter. Before that, I worked on Espresso.
In my free time, I climb rocks, do yoga, eat burritos and go on adventures with my wife and dog.
Want to say hello? Email me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>